# Walid H Khan

www.linkedin.com/in/walidhkhan (480) 544-4705 | walidhkhan@gmail.com Chandler, AZ 85249

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

Business professional with an established work ethic and capability to solve organizational problems in order to accomplish goals. Demonstrated ability to work with a team or independently while supporting a desire to thrive within a growing organization. Experience with full-cycle accounting, financial reporting, operations, and fiscal correspondence.

#### **EDUCATION:**

# **Bachelor of Science in Accounting**

08/2016 - 12/2018

**GPA 3.11** 

Grand Canyon University | Phoenix, Arizona

Clubs & Societies: Accounting Society and Finance/Economics Club

#### **EXPERIENCE:**

## Operations Associate | Kohl's | Chandler, AZ

09/2020 - Present

- Operated in Kohl's omnichannel, amazon, shoes, home, kids, and point-of-sale departments.
- Executed pricing & signing changes, assisted with processing freight, replenished and re-stocked floor inventory.
- Audited backstock inventory, supported merchandising strategy, and assisted operations with special projects.

### Associate Accountant | CBRE | Phoenix, AZ

03/2019 - 06/2020

- Managed full-cycle accounting activities for nine commercial properties (up to \$3.5 million worth in assets).
- Prepared month-end financial reporting packages within an accurate and timely manner in compliance with Real Estate Accounting Policies and Procedures.
- Created, posted, and re-classed journal entries.
- Initiated wire transfers, performed credit applications, processed check runs, created accruals, inputted lease revisions and manual billings.
- Analyzed and reviewed financial statements including the general ledger, income statement, balance sheet, trial balance, and receivables ledger.
- Calculated sales taxes and asset management fees due.
- Ensured expenses, cash receipts, owner's distributions, funding requests and other transactions for the accounting period were accurately posted.
- Reconciled bank statements, general ledger accounts, sales tax calculations, owner's distribution calculations, asset management fees, and cash analysis statements.
- Amended the yearly budget and yearly operating expense form.
- Paid and resolved complications regarding state property tax and real estate tax payments.
- Reviewed A/P invoices and resolved vendor specific A/P issues.
- Reviewed legal real estate documentation and annual CAM / OPX reconciliations.
- Researched and communicated financial information with property managers and clients.

#### Front End Associate | Fry's Food and Drug | Chandler, AZ

05/2018 - 08/2018

- Monitored work of fellow courtesy clerks and trained newly hired associates.
- Acquired and packaged requested items and clearing company property of unwanted items.

#### **SOFTWARE:**

- Fluent with Windows OS, Microsoft Office applications with intermediate understanding of Excel.
- Experience with MRI, Ultimus, Peoplesoft, and Yardi Procedure to Pay software applications.

## **CERTIFICATIONS:**

<u>Certificates</u>: Accounting Fundamentals, Fixed Income Fundamentals, & Reading Financial Statements <u>Licenses</u>: 11524154, 12274836, 11731174 designated by the Corporate Finance Institute